

♣ Profile

Well-qualified mobile developer with advanced skills on Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, SOLID, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares, following good principles and techniques of the Software Engineering. I have more than 3 years of related experience with software development.

★ Favorite technologies



Employment history

Mobile developer at Megaleios

June 2021 - Present

Mobile developer at Bean Softwares

March 2021 - June 2021

Mobile developer at Thalamus Digital

July 2020 - June 2021

Mobile developer at MFIT Personal

January 2020 - May 2020

Education

Computer Science at Univali

February 2020 - Present

English at KNN Idiomas

September 2020 - Present

Projects

Entrepreneur at iCut

May 2021 - Present

A barber appointment app. Available on icut.app

Voluntary coding instructor

May 2021 - Present

Teaching some friends how to code.

Entrepreneur at StudentPlus

August 2018 - April 2021

A study planner. Available on Google Play

Details

Itajaí, SC, Brazil

contact@lucasbatista.me

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

WhatsApp

Website

Skills

TDD

UI/UX Design

DevOps

UML

Design Patterns

SOLID

Clean Architecture

Agile

Languages

English

Hobbies

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.